# Mikhail Krutikhin

Winte256 | in mikhail-krutikhin | ≥ m.krutihin@gmail.com | 1 +381 62 1150 562

# SUMMARY

Has 6+ years of programming experience, 5+ years of specialized experience in frontend, 3+ years of Team Leadership (3+ ppl). Uses Next.js and Nuxt.js

Technical Skills: Javascript/Typescript, React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, HTML, CSS, GIT etc.

Expirienced with Algorithms and data structures.

Recent personal achievement: Initiated and orchestrated the formation of a small group within the company, dedicated to enhancing our Computer Science knowledge.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# Digital Wave Technology

Nov 2023 - Present

- /Stack/: Vue, Pinia, Node.js, graphQL
- \* Key Responsibilities:
  - Pricing system development;
  - Discussing product requirements with the CEO;
  - Conducting code reviews for colleagues;
  - Deep involvement in a unique product;
  - Developing components based on clients' requirements;
  - Fixing bugs on the frontend as well as the backend;
  - Participating in coding interviews;
- \* Achievements:
  - Investigated Camunda environment and integrated it with our system;
  - Developed a fully custom control panel for Camunda Modeler;
  - Developed many complicated components like search with autocomplete.

**DEXART**Jul 2022 - Nov 2023

- /Stack/: Vue, Nuxt, Vercel, Git, CI/CD, OAuth, web3, SSR, BFF
- \* Team and Role Context:
  - Key developer in a compact frontend team, consisting of fewer than 5 professionals.
  - Tasked with the coordination and assignment of frontend-specific duties among a three-person subset of the larger team.
  - Regular connect with backend specialists to ensure seamless integration and functionality.
- \* Key Responsibilities:
  - Managed the development and maintenance of a 2D map interface in Unity
  - Successfully rolled out the dex.art project within stipulated timelines.
  - Engineered a unified system for user authentication and registration, leveraging OAuth, web3, and standard credential methodologies.
  - Developed multi-language support (in excess of five languages), resulting in a twofold surge in advertisement conversions.

#### \* Achievements:

- Played a pivotal role in the transition from Nuxt 2 to Nuxt 3, ensuring continuity and efficiency.
- Played a pivotal role in enhancing the application's performance, significantly reducing bundle sizes and accelerating website load times.

## OTON Technology

Dec 2017 - Jul 2022

- /Stack/: React, Next, Vue.js, Node.js, pm2
- \* Main Tasks:
  - Develop and maintane new frontend solution for manage network business on the web3 technologies.
  - Make a web store which support server-side rendering and ready to high load of visitors.
  - Backend Collaboration: Maintained a continuous dialogue with the backend team to craft cohesive and robust solutions in tandem with frontend requirements.

### \* Results:

- Successfully developed back office frontend solution using React.js on a client and simple static node.js server on a backend which was later transitioned to Vue and some cloud solution for backend. It boosted stability and expedited feature development.
- Oton Market was a big and interesting project and after we finished this project we closed all business requests. I got 2 junior frontend developers in my team.

## TradeSoft Company

May 2017 - Dec 2017

- \* Context
  - Junior frontend developer
  - Studied some technologies like: Vue.js, Docker, Linux, REST API, CI/CD, agile methodology and tests.
  - Collaborated with the backend team to address frontend requirements and integration points.

#### \* Results:

- Played a key role in enhancing the "Parts-Catalogs" frontend, resulting in a more interactive and user-friendly product.
- Demonstrated significant growth and skill acquisition in a challenging and fast-paced environment.
- Contributed to the project's overall success, with "Parts-Catalogs" witnessing increased usability and customer satisfaction during my tenure.

# PROJECTS

#### Some Project

The result of my work in Dexart company. Has over than 20k users every day. Technology frontend foundation is Nuxt+Vercel. Recently was refactored to latest Nuxt.js version and optimized for high load

# EDUCATION

2014 - 2016 Diploma in Information Technology (Incomplete) at Kirov Aviation College

# SKILLS

Some Skills Typescript, Javascript, React, Vue, Next, Nuxt, HTML, CSS, REST, SSR, Algorithms, OAuth, BFF, mobx etc.

Some More Skills English (B1), Russian (Native), Problem-solving, Self-Motivated etc.

Last updated: June 11, 2024